Well, you could ask your AI,
whichever one you're using.
So what's the best way for me to
use you to make money?
You could go in with a vague and
ambiguous question like that and
ask it what it thinks you should
do.
And if you're brand new on that
platform it's probably not gonna
know who you are.
So then what you might wanna do
and it's probably not gonna go
here but you should say,
ask me questions
until you have enough information
about me
to be able to provide me some kind
of alignment
in using you in my world to try to
make money, whatever that is.
Now maybe you work for a company.
Maybe you're working for somebody
else.
Maybe you're a bagger at Sprouts
or somebody that works in the
produce department of Vons or
somebody that's a receptionist at
a roofing company.
Whatever it may be.
Maybe what you could do, and you
have to be careful with this, but
maybe you could find a problem in
your business, the one that you
happen to be working in.
And everybody carries some kind of
experience with them.
where I used to take me three or
four days to write one blog
article, to be able to link it
back to other places in my website
but real links that go to real
valuable pages so that consumers
experience reading that blog
article that I wrote is super
valuable.
Instead of that, I can have AI do
the same thing.
It knows my voice.
It knows how I speak.
It doesn't churn out AI BS.
Six months ago, yeah.
Six months ago, AI churned out
stuff that
was, it was digestible, but it
just wasn't me.
Now that's not the case.
And that's now.